onlinegames96.com 2011-12-26

# Free Games at FreeGames.NET | Play Free Online Flash Games - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for FreeGames.net**

The privacy of our visitors to FreeGames.net is important to us. 

At FreeGames.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit FreeGames.net, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this "behavioral advertising" practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>.

**Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:**

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the[ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
